[Music]
ladies and gentlemen give it up for
Catherine
[Applause]
Blandford Houston Texas
thank you guys thank you please you're
going to Spook the
horse oh I'm so happy to be here guys I
I um I spent the past year and a half
touring across the country for all these
clubs you've had me as a female
headliner for tax breaks it means the
world to me most clubs I go to people
it's the first time they've seen me and
so they come up to me and they're like
oh my God Katherine you're a woman and
I'm like thank you you
and and then they go and you do comedy
and I'm like for that I do
apologize and then they're shocked
they're like but you're not very dirty
and then that that pisses me off cuz I I
want to Houston I want to I just I want
to be like a I want to be a little I
want to be a little rot neck thought so
bad
I just I don't know guys I just I don't
think I have it in me I try so hard but
I think I might be even asexual sorry
Texas
um asexual that's um that's where a
woman dates a
man cuz y seriously even my dirty talk
with my boyfriend I'm like hey you
better hurry up
with this
nonsense this is when I figured it out I
was I was doing a club in Connecticut
that's where your grandparents
live and after my show this manager he
came up to me and he goes Katherine will
you stay for our late late Saturday show
he goes every late late Saturday we have
mail dancers that come in and oh sorry
you guys don't know what that is um
Texas sorry I only do shows for
Christians
okay um male dancers what is that uh
your president president mccon he
starred in a movie about it
um male dancers it's like uh it's like
The Wiggles but for your mom
and it's very interactive okay so I was
like no I'm tired and the manager was
like please Katherine stay so I sat in
the back of the room at my cob salad
light ranch and
this male dancer he came up to me and he
he asked me if I wanted a dance and I
was like no no thank you I'm not a good
dancer and he was like that doesn't
matter
and and he just he tried again this is
what he did he came up behind me and he
purred in the back of my ear and I was
like
no no thank
you you're not really my type I'm more
of a horse
[Music]
girl and then he body rolled down me and
he breeded hot breath into my
badina and I was like no no no just got
off work no more
moisture
and but thanks for the UTI
risk thank God my salad is cranberries
and then he dropped his drawers and out
and a banana hammock
came I was like there's the horse in you
and and then it it just swayed to the
beat cuz he wasn't white
he he sorry that part's redundant I'm
sorry I'm
sorry and he goes you can touch
it now hear me out Christian of Houston
listen
I listen usually I wouldn't have touched
[\h__\h] either
but I know it's in that moment I just I
I don't I just I saw myself in him you
know I was just like I get
it I'm like you you know I I'm a
nighttime Entertainer too who does crowd
work
and and you know sometimes when I do
crowd work and the crowd doesn't want to
participate I know that that sucks
so so out of respect for my fellow
artists when he said you can touch it I
just I just yes and him and this is what
I did y'all this is what I did I go I go
okay here I come
and and I just grabbed my two front
Pinchers and I just went
and I just itsy bitsy spidered his water
spout but I never even looked at it I
looked him in the eyes the whole time
like I was trying to guess a mystery
item what is it a
flute well now it's a
kazoo I say all that to say uh I do I
have a boyfriend and
really I know it's very serious guys we
live together and I know he believes in
me cuz he makes me pay
rent I haven't been promoted yet
proposed to
sorry cuz no matter how much I
squeeze he still pulls
out and that's not a dirty joke houon
that's a clean joke my Catholic
grandmother told me that
she's she said honey when you find a
good one you you hang on to him
and she was so good at it she had 10
kids she was so much more athletic than
me she always stuck The
Landing I know my friends are I don't
know I think they're more athletic than
me too they're all getting promoted I've
been a bridesmaid 14 times guys and I
know I had to go on these Bachelor I'm
so poor I are there is there one right
now this is a weird time this is a weird
thing to do on your
bachelorette is it a second
[Applause]
marriage I mean it's F I like it I like
it for you but you are you're in a
you're at a you're at a comedy show in
an attic on a Friday
night it just kind of feels like you're
like we spent a lot on the first one
maybe
we scale it
back maybe instead of strippers we
listen to a woman talk for an
hour and that's sad you know but maybe
you'll nail it on the third
one sorry I I I did mess that up I'm
sorry I I know it's we're not supposed
to say made anymore
um I've been a bridal intern 14
times you two get
me I was on I was on one of these
employee Retreats right now and before
the big conference
yeah this happened recently I will say
also by the way this happened this trip
that I was on it happened like every
Bachelorette happens okay first of all
every trip starts out everyone's very
cordial everyone's very very polite
they're like no I love your bangs and
and
then and then everybody gets triggered
after a certain point you know for me
it's always like it's always the the
morning after drinking you know you're
so hungry right and you're ready you're
at brunch you're ready to to Chow Down
you know and the girl before you all a
sudden she starts decid she's not going
to be herself anymore you know this is
the day she's going to be good you know
oh you're going to be good now Mary Pig
huh now yeah you think you can be good
good now and she goes I'm just going to
have a summer salad but could you take
off the
food replace it with
wind that's extra I'm okay with
that we as women then we all we get
order guilt so we all order itty bitty
little little salads right and then we
all just we all have to
pretend no it's exactly what I wanted
I can hardly finish it I'm so full on
[Applause]
friendship and then we go home we have
closet pasta
so so I was on this trip and I should
say guys I don't mean to sound like I'm
anti- brunch I'm not I'm not I listen I
love doing comedy I love this but my
passion is drinking in the
morning I love brunch so much I always
leave brunch inspired you know I I I
remember I was at brunch recently and
was with a bunch of girls and I remember
this one girl she was going on and on
about herself I hate her so much she's
my best
friend and I I look past her and I could
see my friend Caitlyn and I could tell
she was really drunk cuz her name's
Caitlyn with a
Y she was that kind of drunk you know
where like like her body was with
us but her eyes
her eyes were back in
Nom she asked me to go to the bathroom
how girlfriend's ask each other to go to
the bathroom right she like leaned over
she was like hey would you and she puked
and her hands I was like well I have to
pee too how you know so we high five
and we went into the bathroom at the
same time and we came out at the same
time but I she was wearing a a romper a
onepiece thing right and and it had a
long zipper in the back and y'all know
if you've ever had a long zipper in the
back to get it up by yourself two-handed
job right one hand H holds a fabric
secure other one Zips it
up but here's the thing Caitlyn didn't
have two free
hands she was holding a drink in one of
her hands
but was Caitlyn going to put that drink
down H was she going to hand it to me no
you're right she doesn't trust anybody
you know how could she she's been
drafted
before
so this is what this DIY bra did she she
didn't even say anything this is what
she did she just she just turned back
around she went back into the bathroom
stall and she kicked open the door right
and then she just she climbed up on top
of the toilet seat backwards right kept
the door open and looked in the
mirror and with her one free hand she
just she just karate chopped that Romper
into her butt
crack do you understand what I'm telling
you
Houston sorry we should get it for the
discount tickets over here they never
get an up close pick of
this okay here we go she get it for the
deacons and the pastors over
here do you understand what I'm telling
you her butt was like I got you girl and
she just Z that mofo
up then she dismounted and did a one leg
twerk to free her Grand
Canyon from its car
harness she looked in the mirror she
fluffed her
pillows and she walked out and I was
like women can do
anything sorry okay so I love brunch
okay I just she I was triggered this day
all right so later on this trip we're at
this party Cove there's a lot of boats
there everyone has everyone has rented
out their own boat we're at the beach
remember the your first one and
uh right and there's like bunch of
people there and they're drinking yeah
yeah and we've got a boat but we're a
bunch of girls in our 30s now and it's
daytime so we're taking shots of breast
milk and
don't knock it till you try it okay let
me if y'all are drinking tonight and you
have a chance to take a shot of your
friend's titty
nectar it doesn't matter how much you
drink you will wake up the next morning
born again okay you my favorite flavor
is Sarah
yeah she's so you can just taste how
good of a mom she is you know it's like
a little bedtime story for your tum time
right here you know oh should say do not
do not try Christine
there's there's something about
Christine you you can tell she still
does cocaine
so so anyways okay so I'm on this boat
right and and I'm feeling a little tipsy
cuz Sarah forgot to pump and
dump and we look over and there's
another boat full of a bunch of girls
and you could tell they're on a bachelor
trip too and but you could tell they
were younger
cuz they're in the
[Laughter]
bikinis and they're taking selfies and
their whole body is in the
picture at a certain point as a woman
you don't take a full body bikini
picture okay at a certain point at a
certain age when you line up for a beach
pick everybody right everybody lines up
we treat it like a loaf of bread the
ends are the worst and
and we'll all like we'll start we'll go
wa
upop and then we'll slowly start backing
into the ocean till about right
here there we go try one more yeah there
we
go Mary Page is like I like my bangs in
that
one but these girls they're much younger
okay and this was this was insane they
um they had this giant raft and they
like started wrestling each other on
this
raft right trying to knock each other
off to one girl's left and then that
girl got to be the
bride
and and these dudes are swimming by and
they just they just notice a bunch of
girls wrestling in their bikinis and
they're
just short circuiting hey
they've never seen anything like that
cuz they're from shreport
so they've only seen their moms do
that one guy can't even handle it he's
like oh my God he's like this is like
girls gone
wall take your tops off and that's when
I got offended I was like
hey why didn't you ask us to do that
no he didn't have to we already
[Applause]
pumping and then he heard me so he
noticed us then he clocked that there
was two Bachelorette groups so he goes
hey he
goes why don't your bride fight their
bride and then all the guys were like
yeah
and then the water got all cloudy
and like what is that oh my
God it tastes like
Christin but arbra she wasn't have right
she's elegant she's from North
Carolina
uh she goes she goes she goes no she
goes I won't fight she goes but I'll
offer up one of my
maids and then of course she just
pointed to me cuz I don't have kids or
eyelash
extensions I should tell you guys that
joke used to be hair extensions
but um
[Applause]
whatever so I was like God I was like I
don't want to do this I'm in my 30s now
you know but you're a bridal intern so
you got to do what the boss set so I
just had to get on this raft and
just Mortal Kombat square up just across
from this 20-year-old feral cat he just
this scrawny
Rachel foaming white Claw at the
M I'm a marketing major
my phone's dead do you have a
charger sorry
emia
and it was one of those moments in my
life we've all had this moment where you
see somebody younger and then you
realize how much you've elevated as a
person I was just looking at her like
[\h__\h] I used to be
you do you remember when you're 20 when
you didn't eat cuz you were trying to
say scrawny cuz you're trying to find a
mate you know cuz you needed shelter
right you didn't want to live with your
17 roommates anymore you know but I was
like now I'm good now I live with an
accountant in the suburbs and we got an
instapot you know you don't you're not
horny anymore you know you don't have to
pretend like you like butt stuff
anymore now it's all like prepared you
know you got sexy time circled on the
calendar every other
Tuesday he comes home you clock in you
do your three positions you clock out
you're like whoa 4 minutes 12 seconds
that that was a long one yeah we're
going to have to use the massage gun
tonight so anyways I was like I've been
out of the game she's going to take me
sure have I had to square up right and
when they said go she she lunged at me
but then she slipped off me cuz she stol
her 20s and wears tanning
oil I'm in my 30s now so I have SPF 90
and Botox
in so I didn't move a
muscle when I just got her in a headlock
and I just whispered forgive your father
and she slipped on her tears and fell in
I don't know I maybe I grew up a little
bit sheltered I I think I I had like I
was one of those kids that played by
myself a lot I had a big imagination I I
grew up in Kentucky I was around horses
I always wanted to be like a cow girl
right but my cousins always made fun of
me cuz they were a lot more country than
me they said I was a city kid cuz I grew
up on a
Colac
and I will say though we had different
childhoods okay the biggest difference
between a country kid and a city kid is
the country kids they they grow up with
farm animals right and they're a lot
more exposed to the circle of life like
City kids were a lot more sheltered you
know when we have a pet we put a little
oh we'll put a little sweater on them a
that cute and Country kids they put
butter on theirs
and and they eat it okay country kids
they see death before breakfast and then
they have that death for breakfast
I remember even recently I went to my
cousin's farm that she's raising her
three kids on and I was talking to Knox
that's her oldest kid he's six he's
telling me how he's helping his daddy
with the baby calves and I was like well
that's so cool KN what are you what are
you doing you help him feed bottles and
he goes no I got to throw rocks to the
buzzards cuz when the Cals are born the
buzzers like to cir around up top and
then they dive down down and they Peck
the C's eyeballs till they can't see no
more and then they can't nurse and after
a few days they starve to death then the
buzzers get to eat them for supper so I
got the rocks of the buzzards cuz Daddy
says the government won't let us shoot
the
[Music]
bastards I was like yeah I get it now I
said
I I mean I did I did the same thing
man when I was your age I had to I had
to feed my Geral
so and one time it disappeared and my
mom was like don't worry it just got to
shed its winter coat and sure enough
next day reappear a whole new
[Music]
color I have this like little brown boy
Jal next day white girl rabbit what's
up I'm telling you these country people
they are so much more at ease with death
I even remember when I was 6 years old
my parents took me to the Kentucky State
horse park for my birthday cuz I was
obsessed with horses you got to go it's
in Lexington Kentucky there's horses you
can pet there's horses you're not
allowed to pet but you can look them in
the eyes and
cry it's Disneyland for Middle
children I'm so excited I'm six my
birthday party right I'm standing
outside the front of the park and I'm
looking at I'm looking at a statue of a
a f famous racehorse named man of war
when all a sudden this hillbilly fairy
shows
up out of a tobacco
Cloud he looks like Tinker bill you know
and he leans over he goes oh man a war
down there and I was
like what and he goes the man a war down
there and I was like oh I'm sorry I have
a boyfriend
and and he goes oh the whole man of war
is buried down there he goes usually
when horses die we got to chop them up
and I was like oh I'm six
um I know I'm a big kid now but this is
day one so that's that's a lot to take
in and he just doubles down he goes
usually we cut out the heart and Hooves
and just bury that represent Spirit and
the speed and I was like oh did my mom
hire you for the party um
I go what do you do with the Unicorn he
goes what I was like well the magic part
he goes oh I'm sorry I have a girlfriend
and
he the thing my country family is most
proud about me for is not selling out
theaters I see
you it's a
rat um
My
Demo don't get the ceiling in this
shot no this is actually this isn't this
is I don't I'm very rich this isn't I'm
very successful um this
is this show this is actually just a
fundraiser
[Music]
uh so that this 2000 seat theater can
finish their
roof it's cuz I I also I get to go
across the country and open up for David
Spade as his body
double we recently we got we booked a
private gig so he got for himself and
all's openers he got us a private jet
and I was so excited cuz I I've flown
fourth class my whole life I'm like I've
never written on one so I get on this
private jet I have to take a private
tinkle
I'm and I don't know if you guys have
been on no you haven't
um you're here anyways H
okay but I can't find the bathroom
because there's no sign so all in it the
pilot comes out and he he kind of first
he kind of scoffs at me you know like
the valet scoffs at you when you show
him how you get in through your trunk
and then he points to this velvet bench
that I was sitting on and he lifts it up
and he goes we hide the toilet seat
underneath and it blew my mind I was
like what that's some rich people Hunger
Games [\h__\h] right there I was like my
people we don't have the toilet we come
from a land called coach and we have
signs because we solids
and I started spiraling I'm like we even
we even play games with our potties okay
so I'm from a land called Louisville
Kentucky where they have the Kentucky
Derby has anyone ever heard of it before
okay okay well red okay front row okay
so what it is if you don't know it's
this fancy event where where where where
wealthy people they watch these animals
running around circles you know and
after every race you can see some of
them freaking out oh [\h__\h] cuz they just
lost their son's college
fund on an animal named buckle up
buttercup
but at the Derby they don't let us
Hillbillies in the stand they Corral Us
in the Enfield so we're there watching
the horses race and and we get foam
while we're like oh I want to do that
home my
moonshine so we have ourselves something
called portapotty racing okay do y'all
know what porta potties are I want to
make sure okay okay you never know my
tickets are expensive so you know
um okay so what Porta poot Rising is uh
if you don't know porta potties um
they're uh I just remember the first
time I saw a porta potty I didn't know
what it was I just saw people like lined
up and they were so excited to get
inside you know they were like oh my
hurry up I I was like oh
my what is in
there I grew up very Catholic so I
thought they were little confessionals
cuz the people just they look so worried
before they got in you know and then
they got out they were so relieved so
I okay so Port by racing what you what
you do is you find a line of these guys
okay that's a godm made Landmark you can
read about it in Genesis and
uh and you go up to the first one of the
line and you ask a man to help you up to
the very tip top of it and he always
does because you have a sunnd dress on
and then uh oh he looks just like you I
I KN okay now I
Clum okay and then the name of the game
is to try and run across the top of the
porta potties without falling in it's
like the floor is lava but
worse cuz it's human lava do you get
it listen if you fall in you're going to
wish it was real lava all right you
would just die but you don't and then
you just have to remember it at Catholic
Mass the next
morning now if you get pretty far and
you haven't fallen in yet then there's
dudes on the ground that are going to
get excited you know cuz now you're
their Redneck Ninja Warrior they're like
oh my God she's really doing it and they
can't help themselves they get so
excited they they'll throw full beer
bottles at your head cuz that's how
their dad showed them they were
proud and then if you dodge all the
bottles full of love
and you make it to the very end then you
get to get arrested
and and then you get to go to jail and
you get to talk to your dad
again anyways I said all that to the
pilot and
uh he was
like you belong on
Frontier it has been it has been a wild
adventure this year like touring and I
it's been crazy I would I will say like
I'm a different person now you know like
i' I've gone everywhere and I I know I
kind of seem like one of you but I'm not
I
am I know I seem like oh yeah I grew up
around country people and I did but I'm
just different than you guys now and I
feel like it's probably I'm going to
lose you you know you're like I like her
she's relatable but I'm I'm so rich now
no I have so much money and
uh I'm about to brag on it for a second
and I know we shouldn't talk numbers but
I just bought a brand new 2013 Moz
dub yeah maybe some of you work hard you
can afford one too
okay can I tell you guys when I went to
go look at the car first time ever
looking at a car I'm looking at it
there's another adult couple my looking
to buy it I'm like oh good for them
theyve made it too
but but they tell me they're thinking
about buying it for their teenage
daughter and I'm like oh okay that just
got embarrassing yeah I was like grow up
buy your own
car so I tried to deter the dab from
buying it but I was honest with him I go
look I go listen you don't want to buy
this Mazda for your teenage daughter I
go I had a mozda when I was growing up
and there's a lot of room in the back
is there something in your eye like
what this is true but this is it wasn't
me back there it was my friends back
there with their boyfriends sorry okay
it was my friends they're always like
don't say boyfriend cther don't put a
label on it it was my friends back there
with their high school volleyball
coaches okay sorry sorry sorry I messed
up did you coach okay um
and my friends they were cool in high
school I wasn't that cool but they would
have me hang around because whenever
they hooked up they needed somebody on
Lookout and I was available and and and
then they figured out they could just
hook up in the back of my car while I
drove around you know cuz there's the
girls in high school that got around and
then there's just the girl I got them
around so it's fine I do comedy now and
uh but I remember the first time my
friend asked me to do it she was like
will you drive us and I was like that's
fine you know just let me know where to
go and so Kon was in the back and she
was like just don't stop I'm almost
there
and
I I was like well it's a COR a sex I
I left or right yeah and she just said
it again she's like I'm almost there you
I was where [\h__\h] you know
yeah but anyway she never got there
um you remember high
school we wasted so much gas that
summer just trying to get there
I remember while they were hooking up
they would uh they would ask me for
privacy they would be like please
Catherine we can hear your heavy
breathing
and so while I'm driving I would just
have to scoot my driver's seat all the
way forward and then lean it all the way
forward until my Chin's on the wheel
right and I didn't play volleyball so I
don't know what kind of drills you
taught these girls
I don't know if they were doing burpees
I'm not sure but eventually while I'm
driving they would just start hitting
the back of my driver's seat over and
over and over again till it got kind of
weird you know cuz like now I'm grooving
along with
them I'm like a dance mom I'm behind the
scenes but I know all the
moves I'm May sexual now but I swear I
used to have three SS I swear to God I
was on the driver seat yeah my parents
knew that I snuck out cuz they have the
Mazda logo imprinted into my
forehead so anyways I said all this to
the salesman and
uh would you believe it he showed me you
guys are the 2013 it has something uh
called a like a back it up camera and I
was like they can watch now I was like
[Applause]
no kids these days you know I did not
need the
visuals the neck pain was enough
my friends are so much you know more
sexual than me so they're they're even
getting married
twice and the the weirdest thing is is
like we're in our 30s now and my friends
they they're going on their Bachelorette
trips for their second marriage and they
still want to they still want to go to
Miami and I'm like all right yeah let's
let's get one more
disease it's so weird like that they'll
want to go to a club you know but but
I'm like but you're a country music fan
you know but I guess this is like my
friend this is her last chance to to
grind with Ricardo before she marries
Rick you
know pops out of Henry that soaks all
the Hope out of her
tits I get
it so this is what'll happen right we
have to now get into the club this is
our bride this is her last dying wish
before her next marriage and
so we can't risk you know standing in
line all night and then maybe not
getting to the club one of the
bridesmaid she' be like don't worry
worry guys I got you I'm going to text
the club promoter and we're like what
Stephanie how did you get his
number you're a mother of four
and she's like shut up I manifested it
and
uh and then she'll text him and she'll
be like hi Ricardo
uh uh I'm with a bunch of hot girls we
want to get into your club tonight for
VIP which means you skip the line you
get VIP service right and then he'll
text back and he'll be like
I you can't see him but you know you
know what I mean you can you know you
can like hear a crunch through the phone
you're like what why is there a Doritos
bag in your crotch
and and it'll be like I might have one
VIP spot
left send me a
picture and what he wants he wants a
picture of the group right to make sure
his VIP spots looking right looking
tight you
know and we know that too so we know we
got to deliver in this
picture but here's the sticky situation
hou we're
uh we're working with a select roster of
[Laughter]
girls you pick up what I'm putting down
right now
these are girls you know that the girl
picked to be her bridesmaides you know
they've been influential in her life
they've been good girls to her but some
of
them they're just good girls
so we have to put our first string in
the front
[Applause]
row and then some of us find out oh
we're middle row girls right and that
that hurts but
listen but by the way in this situation
I'm not a front row girl either okay I'm
a middle row girl okay I listen I'm
front row if we're trying to sneak into
a preena dog show that's me okay you can
buy that my baby's about to go on you
know I got a glue fur extensions on to
her say that's
me but a club front row girl that's a
girl with some Peaks and valleys to her
right that's the girl when you're with
her you can do you can you can hold on
to more than just memories you
know so those they they got to play
offense right make sure their
personality shine and
then us middle world girls now we got to
play defense and we got to we got to box
out that one girl into the
Shadows cuz listen Rebecca listen your
big
heart it's not going to get us into the
club tonight
okay but she doesn't realize it though
because in Huntsville Alabama she's an
11 but in Miami she's a bouncer
[Applause]
I'm not that great in a club either you
know I listen again like I said I love
doing comedy but my dream was to be an
exotic
dancer but I realized that dream had to
be squashed early on I remember I
remember even my first dance with boys
right I realize I can't I can't really
twerk you know when I Twerk it it feels
like I'm it feels V you know I feel like
I'm trying to stab you with my whole
body I remember my first dance with boys
it was a middle school mixer and I was
ready I was like these boys they're not
ready for these doublea's
I about to rev them
up and then I got there and I realized
all the cool girls were wearing
something different than me they all had
on some like abramian
Fitch they had a little 10 point buck
right that little right here what I
didn't have that on what I had on if my
mom was going to splurge she'd take her
Kohl's
cash and she give me some like knockoff
American
Eagle you know what that is like I had a
little Eagle right here but if you look
closely there was a squirrel and it's
[Applause]
Talent so so
I'm I'm at this dance I'm in my dead
scroll shirt and
and and there's a DJ there right and he
starts playing Lil
John U that's rap music
Texas he's like mord and Sons but
faster you know Lumin ear has that song
that's like hey how RAB used to like Hey
Ho so it's different not the same
so DJ he starts playing Lil John right
and then all the cool girls and their
abocom fit they Rush the dance floor and
they start twerking but very stiff cuz
we were white Catholics
so just picture a litter of scared
Golden Retriever puppies out
there more bones than me you know more
clanking then
clapping and I've never seen seen
twerking before in my life oh this is
the first time the only other dance I'd
been to before this was a father
daughter
dance they didn't have that
there I'm not from lck
Texas some of you are some of you made
it
out I'm just studying I'm right I'm
watching watching the girls do a little
maate and call W what's up o o oo coach
what's up coach
oo and the males will come up behind
them and then they they just they just
they just fit together like a little
puzzle
piece they do the little standing up
night dance you know what I mean you
seen Animal Planet before
right and as I'm studying them I'm by
the water fountains
right as I'm studying them this little
boy this little bottom feeder comes up
behind me and he
just and I could taste his mom's beef
stroken off through his
braces and I was like I think I'm going
to give it to
him I think I'm about to lose my
virginity but but
listen but here's the thing
I'm very white too I to me a beet is
just a vegetable
so it gets a big laugh in Atlanta
[Laughter]
uh I feel like some of you like what
else is
it I don't have time I can't
so but I just remember like thinking I
could twerk this is what I did I just I
shimmed on up to this young gentleman
and then this is what I did with my body
this I just I just played I just minded
the words with my with my body I just I
just went to the window and I just did a
tight little square and then to the wall
and I got real
stiff and then the whole time that boy's
pelvis just had a hard time
guessing where I was headed to next
until eventually he had to detach so he
could puke from motion
sickness and that is that young man's
coming out
story thank you thank you you you some
Tex thank
you I don't know I don't know uh what
everybody else follows or if you do if
you if you used to be I I was very
Catholic I like like went to Catholic
Middle School all girls catholic High
School my favorite color is plaid skirt
I one bread one body favorite backstory
Boy song
okay but us cats we
um we had this little book called The
Bible and inside there were little fairy
tales
and and I remember even when I was young
some of the stories really tripped me up
sometimes there were stories in the
Bible about how God would use one person
as aond to teach another person a lesson
right there was a story that always
tripped me up it was about a man his
name was Abraham was and um what's up
I'm Abraham I'm 482 years old and I'm
running for president and uh I'm just
kidding I don't know what you did back
then maybe Pharaoh I'm not and but he he
really wanted a son right so God finally
granted him a son and he was so pumped
he's like what's up son and and what he
loved him right then one day God showed
up and he was
like Abraham if you really love me you'd
slay your only son for me and this is
back in the day so SLE is not good yet
okay
th this is not Pride week SLE Texas okay
this is this is your grandparents Good
Friday SLE okay this this is like no
don't SLE you know it's like no you
better not SLE girl it's not good
and and Abraham doesn't want to do it
he's like no it's my kid but he's like
all right God anything for you babe and
so he's like how am I going to do this
right so he goes to his s he's like hey
son I have a great idea let's go camping
and and so then they hike up to the top
of this mountain right and they get up
there and Abraham's like oh my God what
is that an altar up there what what are
the odds oh my God I'm literally
dead how long has that been up there oh
my God climb on it see if it's
sturdy and then right before Abraham is
about to ah slay his only son God shows
up and he's like
punked my God I can't be you do that ah
you're so obsessed with me
and you've seen them practical jokers
so but the story doesn't talk about
Abraham's son after that who's probably
just climbing off the table
like no I thought no I thought it was
funny too I did no I no no I just I I
cry when I laugh
no when I'm happy I look devastated
I and that's how the Bible teaches us
where daddy issues come
from and these were the stories as a kid
that stuck with me right and then I grew
up and I went to high school and I I
became a Catholic [\h__\h] as a prophecy
fortold and I was dating this guy and
then I cheated on him but I did the
right thing and I told him the truth I
was like listen God made me do
it you know and he's
devastated and
um imagine it but
younger and then the next day my family
we go out of town for Christmas vacation
and we don't make it back in town for
the big like high school New Year's Eve
party and we get back down the next day
and my boyfriend calls me and he's like
hey um I got to talk to you about
something can I take you out to a nice
dinner and I'm like yeah it's the least
you could do after what you made me do
to you
so so we go to this nice dinner I'm
eating my crunch trap
Supreme and he he goes listen I got to
tell you something he goes you know
things got crazy at the party last night
he was like I was so upset about what
happened with you and I just I just I
ended up hooking up with car's cousin
and I was like what I was like how did
this happen he's like I don't know we
were in the back of a raap four I was
like not even a Mazda you kidding
me and by the way car's cousin was this
girl who used to live in our hometown
but she moved away to New York to become
a big-time model and she was modeling
for all the big names like Sears and
koh's and then the dagger in the wound
was the next day now there's a write up
in our local newspaper about how car's
cousin is now playing in a TV show show
so I'm like not only she my dad's
cataloges but now she's on my TV so I
start following her career just to make
sure she wasn't going to go anywhere and
I went far away to a land called South
Carolina for college and I would ask my
friends at College I would ask them if
they knew who she was to see if she was
a household name I'd be like do you guys
know who Carrie's cousin is and they
would be like we don't we don't even
know who Carrie
is and I would be like yes says right
one point for
me and then one day my friend my college
friend she comes up to me and she goes
um Katherine I I have some hard news to
tell you she goes um do you know that
girl you're obsessed with and I go
no I don't know what you're talking
about she goes the world pool model I
like yeah maybe
maybe she goes um I think she's about to
be really famous she's about to start in
this movie called Hunger Games
yeah so listen Houston listen it's not
that I don't think Jennifer Lawrence
deserves the career she's
had listen I'm just saying okay maybe
she's gotten to where she's gotten to
because God was trying to teach me a
lesson
okay God was like oh you're going to be
unfaithful Catherine huh I turned water
into wine I can turn someone's cousin
into a celebrity real quick okay I
remember when she told me she was like
like it's called Hunger Games and I was
like okay I've tried keto
before she was like no it's going to be
really famous she's like the hero in it
it's based off of three books you know I
was like I mean come
on I mean she's the hero she died in the
first one right like my lord and savior
he only needed one
book Houston thank you guys so so
freaking much I so love you
guys I love you I love you I love you
thank you this been a dream come j thank
you guys thank you thank you thank you
thank
you thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
guys you ready to do your little skits
tonight no it's like a big girl set who
do you think you are
Beyonce no I mean we're like a cool Duo
you'd be nothing without me well you
still be working at pfchangs without me
whatever you little wannabe Catholic
cowgirl but hey hope you have a good
show tonight
[Music]